Guide to the Consumer Reports. Board of Directors records, 1916-2015 and undated RL.11787
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Consumer Reports. Board of Directors records
1916-2015 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Consumer Reports (Firm)
RL.11787
60.0 Linear Feet
Consumer Reports is a product testing and consumer advocacy nonprofit organization based in Yonkers, N.Y., founded in 1936. The Consumer Reports Board of Directors records include correspondence, meeting minutes, clippings, financial and status reports, pamphlets and other printed materials. Topics include general operations, Board memberships and resignations; budgets and financial performance, building maintenance and facility site planning; Consumers Union mission and philosophy; litigation; personnel and pension policies; publication and subscription status; research and technical activities. Board members and correspondents represented in the collection include Betty Furness, Clarence Ditlow, Colston Warne, Marjorie East, and Ralph Nader. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: General Files; Board Meetings; President (Colston Warne); Treasurer; Correspondence; Commmittees; Board Members; Elections; Reports to the Board from Outsiders.
Biographical / Historical
Consumer Reports is a product testing and consumer advocacy nonprofit organization based in Yonkers, N.Y., founded in 1936.
The Board of Directors provide policy oversight and strategic planning for the organization. The first Board was established with the founding of Consumers Union in 1936. Original Board members were: Robert Brady (economist, later Director of Western Consumers Union); Heywood Broun (journalist, co-founder of The Newspaper Guild); Osmond Fraenkel (lawyer, co-founder of The Lawyers Guild); Abraham J. Isserman (labor lawyer, Counsel for the American Civil Liberties Union); Arthur Kallet (engineer, first Director of Consumers Union); Charles Marlies (chemical engineer); Dewey Palmer (physicist); A. Philip Randolph (labor organizer, co-founder of The Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, the first black-led union in the United States); Bernard Reis (lawyer and accountant, first Treasurer of Consumers Union); and Rose Schneiderman (Women's Trade Union League, labor organizer, feminist, leader in New York's suffrage movement).
Later prospective Board members were invited to apply for admission. Board members originally served 2-year renewable terms.
Access Restrictions
Collection is restricted. Meeting minutes are closed for 25 years from the date of production. Other materials produced by Consumer Reports are closed for 40 years from the date of production.
Provenance
The Consumer Reports. Board of Directors records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2019.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Consumer Reports A.J. Isserman papers
Consumer Reports Arthur Kallet papers
Consumer Reports Colston Warne papers
Collection Overview
The Consumer Reports Board of Directors records include correspondence, meeting minutes, clippings, financial and status reports, pamphlets and other printed materials. Topics include general operations, Board memberships and resignations; budgets and financial performance, building maintenance and facility site planning; Consumers Union mission and philosophy; litigation; personnel and pension policies; publication and subscription status; research and technical activities. Board members and correspondents represented in the collection include Betty Furness, Clarence Ditlow, Colston Warne, Marjorie East, and Ralph Nader. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Consumer advocacy; consumer protection; Product safety; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Warne, Colston E. (Colston Estey), 1900-1987
- General Files, 1936-2006; 1
  - Actions requiring implementation or follow-up, 1963-1972 (Box 1)
  - Actions taken by Board, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Board/Staff retreats, 1965-1979; 5 folders (Box 1)
  - Board background materials, 1960-1970s (Box 1)
  - Duties and responsibilities of officers and directors, 1955 (Box 1)
  - Evolution of CU Board structure, 1936-1971 (Box 1)
  - Executive session, 2006 (Box 3)
  - Highlights of the Tarrytown conference, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Members of Board, 1936-1999; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Motions passed, 1973-1975 (Box 2)
  - Orientation manual, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Orientation manual, 1997-2004; 6 folders (Box 3)
  - Policy resolutions, 1936-1971; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Report--California Study and Auto Division Forward Plan, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Report--Cost reduction stury, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Statements adopted by Board, 1952-1961 (Box 2)
- Board Meetings, 1936-2015; 2
  - Meeting agendas, 1936-1975 (Box 4)
  - Minutes, 1936-1965; 7 folders (Box 4)
  - Minutes, 1965-1972; 12 folders (Box 5)
  - Minutes, 1972; 8 folders (Box 6)
  - Minutes, 1973-1974 Jan.; 11 folders (Box 7)
  - Minutes, 1974 May-Dec.; 7 folders (Box 8)
  - Minutes, 1975 Jan.-1976 May; 8 folders (Box 9)
  - Minutes, 1976 May-1977 Oct.; 9 folders (Box 10)
  - Minutes, 1977 Oct.-1978 June; 9 folders (Box 11)
  - Minutes, 1978 Oct.-1979 Jan.; 10 folders (Box 12)
  - Minutes, 1979 May-Oct.; 8 folders (Box 13)
  - Minutes, 1980; 8 folders (Box 14)
  - Minutes, 1981; 9 folders (Box 15)
  - Minutes, 1981 Oct.-1982 Jan.; 8 folders (Box 16)
  - Minutes, 1982 June-1983 Jan.; 7 folders (Box 17)
  - Minutes, 1983 Jan.-1984 June; 6 folders (Box 18)
  - Minutes, 1984 June-1986 Jan.; 7 folders (Box 19)
  - Minutes, 1986 Jan.-1987 May; 6 folders (Box 20)
  - Minutes, 1987 Oct.-1988 Jan.; 8 folders (Box 21)
  - Minutes, 1988 June-1989 Feb.; 9 folders (Box 22)
  - Minutes, 1989 May-Oct.; 9 folders (Box 23)
  - Minutes, 1990; 10 folders (Box 24)
  - Minutes, 1991 Jan.-1992 May; 13 folders (Box 25)
  - Minutes, 1992 Oct.-1993 Oct.; 10 folders (Box 26)
  - Minutes, 1993 Oct.-1995 Oct.; 15 folders (Box 27)
  - Minutes, 1996 Jan.-1998 Feb.; 11 folders (Box 28)
  - Minutes, 1998 Feb.-1999 May; 11 folders (Box 29)
  - Minutes, 1999 May-2001 May; 12 folders (Box 30)
  - Minutes, 2001 Oct.-2002 Jan.; 8 folders (Box 31)
  - Minutes, 2002 May-Oct.; 7 folders (Box 32)
  - Minutes, 2003 Feb.-Oct.; 9 folders (Box 33)
  - Minutes, 2003 Oct.-2004 June; 8 folders (Box 34)
  - Minutes, 2004 June-2005 Jan.; 8 folders (Box 35)
  - Minutes, 2005 Jan.-May; 8 folders (Box 36)
  - Minutes, 2005 Oct.-2006 May; 7 folders (Box 37)
  - Minutes, 2006 Oct.-2007 May; 7 folders (Box 38)
  - Minutes, 2007 Oct.-2008 May; 8 folders (Box 39)
  - Minutes, 2008 Oct.-2009 Jan.; 7 folders (Box 40)
  - Minutes, 2009 May-2010 May; 8 folders (Box 41)
  - Minutes, 2010 Oct.-2012 Jan.; 7 folders (Box 42)
  - Minutes, 2012 May-2013 Oct.; 8 folders (Box 43)
  - Minutes, 2015 Jan.-May; 4 folders (Box 44)
  - Minutes (compilation binders), 1989-2001; 6 folders (Box 45)
  - Minutes (compilation binders), 1998-2013; 6 folders (Box 46)
- President (Colston Warne), 1939-1979; 3
  - Clippings, 1979 (Box 47)
  - Correspondence, 1941-1974 (Box 47)
  - Dinner honoring Colston Warne, 1979 (Box 47)
  - Reports to Board, 1973-1975 (Box 47)
  - Speaking engagements, 1964-1971 (Box 47)
  - Writings, 1939-1973 (Box 47)
- Treasurer, 1937-1989; 4
  - Accountant's reports, 1939-1959; 11 folders (Box 48)
  - Treasurer's reports, 1937-1949 (Box 49)
  - Treasurer's reports, 1951-1953 (Box 50)
  - Treasurer's reports, 1954-1956 (Box 51)
  - Treasurer's reports, 1957-1959 (Box 52)
  - Treasurer's reports, 1960 (Box 53)
  - Financial statements, 1958-1968; 7 folders (Box 53)
  - Financial statements, 1968-1974; 5 folders (Box 54)
  - Financial statements, 1975-1979; 5 folders (Box 55)
  - Financial statements, 1980-1989; 3 folders (Box 56)
  - Expense chart 1936-1970 (Box 57)
  - Budgets, income, expenditure, 1937-1959; 4 folders (Box 57)
  - Budgets, income, expenditure, 1960-1975; 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Bernard Reis, 1943-1962; 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Edward Reich, 1946-1973 (Box 58)
- Correspondence, 1937-1982; 5
  - 1937-1963, 6 folders (Box 59)
  - 1964-1971, 5 folders (Box 60)
  - 1972-1973, 3 folders (Box 61)
  - 1974-1979, 4 folders (Box 62)
  - 1980-1982, 3 folders (Box 63)
- Committees, 1936-2015 and undated; 6
  - General Files, 1947-1991 and undated; 1
    - Committee functions, undated (Box 64)
    - Committee memberships, 1953-1991 (Box 64)
    - Committee nominations, 1956 (Box 64)
    - Legislative Research Program subcommittee, 1947 (Box 64)
  - Executive Committee, 1936-2010; 2
    - Ballots, 1952-1982 (Box 64)
    - Memos/Correspondence, 1938-1974; 5 folders (Box 64)
    - Memos/Correspondence, 1975-1982; 4 folders (Box 65)
    - Minutes, 1936-1956; 3 folders (Box 65)
    - Minutes, 1957-1982; 8 folders (Box 66)
    - Minutes, 2006-2010 (Box 67)
    - Telephone conferences, 1987-1999; 19 folders (Box 67)
    - Test expenditures, 1958-1966 (Box 68)
  - Nominating Committee, 1937-2010; 3
    - Ballot, with biographical sketches, 1940 (Box 68)
    - Correspondence, 1949-1963, 1970-1974; 7 folders (Box 68)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1980; 3 folders (Box 69)
    - General, 1937-1942 (Box 69)
    - Memos--Committee ballots, 1949-1973; 3 folders (Box 69)
    - Minutes, 1948-1976 (Box 69)
    - Minutes, 2006-2010 (Box 67)
    - Report--Subcommittee on Ballot Information, 1973 (Box 69)
  - Committee on Grants, 1956-1966; 4
    - Grant application--Peabody College, 1956 (Box 69)
    - Report on grants since 1952, 1966 (Box 69)
  - Education and Grants Committee, 1960-1974; 5
    - Applications, 1966-1968 (Box 69)
    - Applications, 1966-1970; 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Consumer Organization Project, 1973 (Box 70)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1974; 3 folders (Box 70)
    - Memoranda, 1960-1964 (Box 70)
    - Memoranda, 1965-1973; 2 folders (Box 71)
    - Minutes, 1961-1973; 2 folders (Box 71)
    - Report: Help for Low-Income Consumers, 1963 (Box 71)
    - Reports, 1971-1973; 2 folders (Box 71)
    - Correspondence--Media and Consumer Foundation, 1972-1974 (Box 71)
    - Grants material for Board meetings, 1972; 4 folders (Box 71)
    - Grants material for Board meetings, 1973-1974; 7 folders (Box 72)
    - Report--Arthur Carstens: The Los Angeles Teenager as a Consumer, 1967 (Box 72)
    - Report--Baltimore Urban League, 1964 (Box 72)
    - Report--Charles Firestone, 1967 (Box 72)
    - Report--National Consumer Congress: The Supermarket Project, 1974 (Box 72)
    - Report--Senoras en Asentamientos de Reforma Agraria: Proyecto de Motivacion, 1972 (Box 72)
    - Report--Tufts University: Consumer Project Evaluation, 1972 (Box 72)
  - Public Affairs and Organizational Interests Committee, 1974-1976; 6
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1974-1976 (Box 72)
  - Finance Committee, 1955-1990; 7
    - Budget reports, 1975-1979; 7 folders (Box 73)
    - Budget reports, 1980-1982; 4 folders (Box 74)
    - Budget reports, 1983-1990; 5 folders (Box 75)
    - Memos/Correspondence, 1955-1977; 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Minutes, 1959-1976, 1979; 4 folders (Box 75)
  - Policy Committee, 1938-1976; 8
    - Memos/Correspondence, 1960-1965 (Box 76)
    - Minutes, 1961-1970; 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Policies established by Board, 1938-1976 (Box 76)
    - Report: Comments to 1956 questionnaire, 1957; 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Report: Help for Low-Income Consumers, 1963 (Box 76)
    - Report: Questionnaires, 1951-1955; 3 folders (Box 76)
    - Summaries and recommendations, 1956 (Box 76)
  - Other Committees, 1937-2015; 9
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Board Structure and Function, 1970 (Box 77)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Budget and Financial Performance--Minutes, 1989-1993; 5 folders (Box 78)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Budget and Financial Performance--Telephone conference, 1988-1993; 3 folders (Box 78)
    - Ad Hoc Operations Committee--Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 77)
    - Ad Hoc Operations Committee--Reis-Freedman transcript, 1957 (Box 77)
    - Ad Hoc Operations Committee--Report, 1957; 2 folders (Box 77)
    - Archives Committee, 1973-1989 (Box 77)
    - Audit Committee--Minutes, 1990-1999; 9 folders (Box 78)
    - Audit Committee--Minutes, 2005-2010; 2 folders (Box 80)
    - Audit Committee--Minutes, 2015; 2 folders (Box 79)
    - Auto Test Track Land Search Committee, 1973, 1986; 2 folders (Box 77)
    - Board Performance Audit Committee (Walker Sandbach), 1971-1973; 3 folders (Box 77)
    - By-Laws Committee, 1958-1993 (Box 77)
    - Conflict of Interest Committee--Minutes, 1987 (Box 77)
    - Conflict of Interest Committee--Minutes, 2006-2010 (Box 80)
    - Consumer Activity Committee, 1948 (Box 77)
    - Education Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 77)
    - Finance and Budget Committee--Preliminary budgets, 2001-2002 (Box 80)
    - Finance and Budget Committee--Telephone conference call, 1994-1999; 8 folders (Box 78)
    - Finance and Performance Oversight Committee--Minutes, 2006-2010; 2 folders (Box 80)
    - Finance and Performance Oversight Committee--Minutes, 2015; 2 folders (Box 79)
    - Governance Committee--Minutes, 2006-2010 (Box 80)
    - Innovation and Experimentation Committee, 1971-1975 (Box 77)
    - Investment Committee--Minutes, 1990-1998; 3 folders (Box 78)
    - Pension Committee--Correspondence/Proposals, 1957-1972 (Box 81)
    - Pension Committee--Financial statements, 1962-1972 (Box 81)
    - Pension Committee--Management pension plan, 1981-1982 (Box 81)
    - Pension Committee--Minutes, 1951-1977 (Box 81)
    - Pension Committee--Minutes, 1998 (Box 78)
    - Pension Committee--Non-qualified plan, 1967 (Box 81)
    - Pension Committee--Pension management, 1948-1974 (Box 81)
    - Pension Committee--Reports, 1950-1977 (Box 81)
    - Pension Committee--Trust indentures, 1949-1950 (Box 81)
    - Project Cost Committee, 1958 (Box 81)
    - Real Estate Committee (Orangeburg), 1971-1984; 3 folders (Box 81)
    - Search Committee for Executive Director--Candidates, 1973-1974 (Box 81)
    - Search Committee for Executive Director--Candidates, 1973-1974; 2 folders (Box 82)
    - Search Committee for Executive Director--Memoranda and minutes, 1973-1974; 2 folders (Box 82)
    - Special Committee to Investigate and Report on Management-Labor Difficulties in Consumers Union, 1948 (Box 82)
    - Special Committee to Study Reallocation of Functions, 1937 (Box 82)
    - Subcommittee to Deal with Devising Format for Indicating Board Performance in Addition to Attendance, 1973 (Box 82)
    - Technical Policy Committee, 1957-1973 (Box 82)
    - Washington Office Committee, 1973 (Box 82)
    - Yonkers Relocation Subcommittee, 1988-1989; 4 folders (Box 82)
    - Yonkers Relocation Subcommittee, 1989 (Box 83)
      Scope and Contents
      City of Yonkers Industrial Development Agency, Civic Facility bond documents, 2 vols.
- Board Members, 1916-1995 and undated; 7
  - Aaron, Harold, 1938-1988 (Box 84)
  - Anderson, Eleanor, 1942-1946 (Box 84)
  - Banzhaf, John III, 1968-1970 (Box 84)
  - Berberian, John, 1975 (Box 84)
  - Beube, Frank, 1944-1947 (Box 84)
  - Bivens, Gordon, 1967-1974 (Box 84)
  - Brady, Robert, undated (Box 84)
  - Brunn George, 1965-1978 (Box 84)
  - Campbell, Persia, 1961-1974 (Box 84)
  - Canoyer, Helen, 1951-1963 (Box 84)
  - Clark, Lincoln, 1953-1975 (Box 84)
  - Claybrook, John, 1992 (Box 84)
  - Colby, William, 1953-1956 (Box 84)
  - Crosby, Alexander, 1935-1948 (Box 84)
  - Cross, Hartley, 1943-1948 (Box 84)
  - Davis, Jerome, 1947-1974 (Box 84)
  - Denenberg, Herbert, 1972-1979 (Box 84)
  - Ditlow, Clarence, 1974-1976; 4 folders (Box 84)
  - Ditlow, Clarence, 1973-1974; 2 folders (Box 85)
  - East, Marjorie, 1957-1973; 3 folders (Box 85)
  - Edmonston, Phil, 1979-1981 (Box 85)
  - Epstein, Samuel, 1974-1981 (Box 85)
  - Fraenkel, Osmond, 1952-1974 (Box 85)
  - Frese, Robert, 1961-1963 (Box 85)
  - Furness, Betty, 1967-1994; 4 folders (Box 85)
  - Gilman, James, 1936-1947 (Box 85)
  - Goldwater, Leonard, 1955-1978 (Box 85)
  - Gordon, Leland, 1942-1975 (Box 85)
  - Grundfest, Harry, 1944-1947 (Box 86)
  - Hall, Helen, 1949-1967 (Box 86)
  - Haller, Willliam, 1957-1965 (Box 86)
  - Harap, Henry, 1968 (Box 86)
  - Hayakawa, S.I., 1946-1968 (Box 86)
  - Hellerstein, Jerome, 1944-1980 (Box 86)
  - Herrmann, Robert, 1970-1978 (Box 86)
  - Hochman, Julius, 1936-1943 (Box 86)
  - Hoffman, George, 1960-1966 (Box 86)
  - Isserman, Abraham, 1944-1978 (Box 86)
  - Kern, Paul, 1945-1955 (Box 86)
  - Klein, Emanuel, 1944-1947 (Box 86)
  - Krughoff, Robert, 1976 (Box 86)
  - LaFollette, Bronson, 1968-1976 (Box 86)
  - Lane, Sylvia, 1974-1978 (Box 86)
  - Lee, Stewart, 1964-1978 (Box 86)
  - Lynd, Robert, 1942 (Box 86)
  - MacColl, William, 1947-1978 (Box 86)
  - Malisoff, W.M., 1943 (Box 86)
  - Margolius, Sidney, 1958-1980 (Box 86)
  - Marlies, Charles, undated (Box 86)
  - Maynes, E. Scott, 1969-1993 (Box 86)
  - McInerney, Kathleen, 1952 (Box 86)
  - Morgan, James, 1958-1986 (Box 86)
  - Morse, Richard, 1927-1994; 2 folders (Box 87)
  - Myerson, Bess, 1969-1978 (Box 87)
  - Nader, Ralph, 1966-1976; 4 folders (Box 87)
  - Nader, Ralph, 1966-1976; 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Nelson, Helen, 1965-1976 (Box 88)
  - Noble, Joel, 1995 (Box 88)
  - O'Connell, Jeffrey, 1970-1974 (Box 88)
  - Outland, George, 1940-1956 (Box 88)
  - Pabst, William, 1957-1973 (Box 88)
  - Palmer, Dewey, 1956 (Box 88)
  - Palmer, Frank, 1936-1973 (Box 88)
  - Pooler, Rosemary, 1988 (Box 88)
  - Price, Ray, 1939-1966 (Box 88)
  - Rautenstrauch, Walter, 1943 (Box 88)
  - Reich, Edward, 1967-1974 (Box 88)
  - Reuter, Richard, 1962 (Box 88)
  - Rosebury, Theodor, 1948-1951 (Box 88)
  - Ross, Madeline, 1946 (Box 88)
  - Schulkind, Adelaide, 1936-1938 (Box 88)
  - Shedlovsky, Theodor, 1952-1980 (Box 88)
  - Sullivan, Patrick, 1965-1973 (Box 88)
  - Troelstrup, Arch, 1957-1994 (Box 89)
  - Villard, Henry, 1966-1970 (Box 89)
  - Warne, Colston, 1916-1971; 2 folders (Box 89)
  - Wendt, Gerald, 1941-1942 (Box 89)
  - Wilcox, Clair, 1944-1954 (Box 89)
  - Williams, C. Arthur, 1978 (Box 89)
  - Wilson, Dean, 1964-1970 (Box 89)
- Elections, 1939-1974; 8
  - Correspondence, 1939-1974 (Box 90)
  - Nominations, 1944-1947 (Box 90)
  - Tabulations, 1942-1972 (Box 90)
- Reports to the Board from Outsiders, 1953-1990; 9
  - Automotive test center site selection (Giffels Associates), 1973 (Box 91)
  - Brady Report on the Status, Function and Prospects of CU (Robert Brady), 1956; 2 folders (Box 91)
  - Conflict of interest, 1980 (Box 91)
  - Development and Testing of a Consumer Oriented Information Dissemination System (Community Systems Foundation), 1968 (Box 91)
  - Ditlow-Nash report on CU, 1973 (Box 91)
  - Economic Cost of Air Pollution (Armour Research Foundation), 1960; 2 folders (Box 91)
  - Educación al consumidor (Instituto Inter-Americano de Ciencias Agrícolas IICA), 1972 (Box 91)
  - Evaluation of Location Alternative (Cresap, McCormick, Paget), 1971 (Box 91)
  - Facility evaluation: Orangeburg (Coopers & Lybrand), 1980 (Box 91)
  - Guide for Starting a Local Service Evaluation Magazine (Washington Center for the Study of Services), 1975 (Box 91)
  - Information Requirement Report (Coopers & Lybrand), 1978; 3 folders (Box 92)
  - Members' Use of Consumer Reports and Buying Guides (Carberry), 1953 (Box 92)
  - Organization of Technical Department (Rogers, Slade and Hill), 1954 (Box 92)
  - Position description, job classification study (Rogers, Slade and Hill), 1954 (Box 92)
  - Proposal by National Academy of Engineering, 1970 (Box 92)
  - Proposal for Laboratory Services ((Foster D. Snell), 1961 (Box 92)
  - Proposal for Preliminary Development and Testing of a Consumer Oriented Information Dissemination System (Community Services Foundation), 1967 (Box 92)
  - Proposed Automotive Research Center (Giffels Associates), 1973 (Box 92)
  - Qualitative Study of Consumer Reports Books (Langer), 1990; 2 folders (Box 92)
  - Recommended Layout for the Promotion and Subscription Operations (Rogers, Slade and Hill), 1954 (Box 92)
  - Report on Special Examination (Arthur Young & Co. Auditors), 1953 (Box 92)
  - Report on Subscriber Comments on the 1956 Questionnaire (George Outland), 1957 (Box 93)
  - State and Local Consumer Organizations (Sorenson), 1972 (Box 93)
  - Survey of Former Subscribers to Consumer Reports, 1970 (Box 93)
  - Survey of Present and Former Subscribers to Consumer Reports (Benson & Benson), 1970 (Box 93)
  - Test of Effects of Warning Overlays on Antacid Commercials (Response Analysis Corporation), 1977 (Box 93)
  - The Wider Challenge: Some Proposals for Consumers Union (Arthur Rowse), 1972 (Box 93)